<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Authors | Liu Bing Lab</title><link>https://kwaihua.github.io/en/authors/</link><atom:link href="https://kwaihua.github.io/en/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Authors</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 07:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://kwaihua.github.io/media/icon_hu4fe0dfe056522f70592819395fc53875_54434_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url><title>Authors</title><link>https://kwaihua.github.io/en/authors/</link></image><item><title>Liu Bing</title><link>https://kwaihua.github.io/en/author/liu-bing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kwaihua.github.io/en/author/liu-bing/</guid><description>&lt;p>The research interests of Prof. Liu Bing mainly focus on the two topics :&lt;/p>
&lt;p>(1) Clinical translation of multi-modal neuroimaging: here we attempt to build clinical useful biomarkers for brain disorders by integrating multi-modal neuroimaging and other omics data, and using novel artificial intelligence technologies. The objective of these studies is to identify quantitative, individualized, generalized and clinically useful imaging biomarkers for the precision diagnosis and personalized treatment of brain disorders, especially for various psychiatric disorders.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>(2) Neuroscience translation of multi-modal data: By combing genome, transcriptome, multi-modal neuroimaging and other data, we attempt to study the heritability of brain networks, the connection between brain networks and genetic variations, to find key genes modulating hub brain regions and important brain connectivity, and finally to reveal the underlying genetic and neural mechanisms of the individual differences in human neurodevelopment, behaviors or brain disorders and to construct dynamic prediction models of individual performance. Our lab has published over 70 research papers in peer-reviewed journals, including Nature Medicine, Nature Communication, Journal of Neuroscience, Schizophrenia Bulletin, Neuropsychopharmacology, NeuroImage etc.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>